mdbg.net 2019-04-24

# MDBG Chinese Dictionary

隐私

## Privacy and cookies

This privacy policy sets out how MDBG uses and protects any information that you give MDBG when you use this website. MDBG may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of MDBG websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof. 

###  Collection and Use of Personal Information 

You can visit the websites of MDBG without revealing any personal information. However, MDBG needs certain personal information if you wish to purchase our products or use certain MDBG services. Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. MDBG will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member's account, and to contact you regarding new products and services. By accessing the services of MDBG and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

###  How we use cookies 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

###  Third part cookies 

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. For more information, see [Google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). 

We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using [Google's Ads Preference Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). See [Google's advertising privacy FAQ](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/#toc-optout) for more information about how to opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie. 

###  Links to other websites 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

###  More information about cookies and disabling cookies 

You can find more information about cookies and how to disable cookies on the following website: [Cookies & You](https://cookiesandyou.com/). 

Tip: Pinyin can be entered with or without tone numbers, e.g. 'nihao' or 'ni3hao3'.
